♪ ♪
♪ THIS IS THE MANIFESTO
OF MOTHER MONSTER. ♪
♪ ♪
♪ ON G.O.A.T, A "GOVERNMENT
OWNED ALIEN TERRITORY" ♪
♪ IN SPACE, A BIRTH OF
MAGNIFICENT AND MAGICAL ♪
♪ PROPORTIONS TOOK PLACE.
BUT THE BIRTH, WAS NOT ♪
♪ FINITE, IT WAS
INFINITE: AS THE WOMBS ♪
♪ NUMBERED, AND THE
MITOSES OF THE FUTURE ♪
♪ BEGAN, IT WAS PERCEIVED
THAT THIS INFAMOUS ♪
♪ MOMENT IN LIFE IS
NOT TEMPORAL. IT IS ♪
♪ ETERNAL. AND THUS BEGAN
THE BEGINNING OF THE ♪
♪ NEW RACE. A RACE WITHIN
THE RACE OF HUMANITY, A ♪
♪ RACE WHICH BARES NO
PREJUDICE, NO JUDGMENT, ♪
♪ BUT BOUNDLESS FREEDOM.
BUT ON THAT SAME DAY, ♪
♪ AS THE ETERNAL
MOTHER HOVERED IN THE ♪
♪ MULTIVERSE, ANOTHER
MORE TERRIFYING BIRTH ♪
♪ TOOK PLACE: THE
BIRTH OF EVIL. ♪
♪ ♪
♪ AND AS SHE HERSELF SPLIT
INTO TWO, ROTATING IN AGONY ♪
♪ BETWEEN TWO ULTIMATE
FORCES THE PENDULUM OF ♪
♪ CHOICE BEGAN ITS DANCE.
ITS SEEMS EASY, YOU ♪
♪ IMAGINE, TO
GRAVITATE INSTANTLY AND ♪
♪ UNWAVERINGLY TOWARD GOOD. ♪
♪ ♪
♪ BUT SHE WONDERED, HOW
CAN I PROTECT SOMETHING
SO PERFECT, ♪
♪ WITHOUT EVIL. ♪
♪ ♪
♪ IT DOESN'T MATTER IF YOU
LOVE HIM, OR CAPITAL H-I-M ♪
♪ JUST PUT YOUR PAWS UP 'CAUSE
YOU WERE BORN THIS WAY, BABY ♪
♪ ♪
♪ MY MAMA TOLD ME
WHEN I WAS YOUNG ♪
♪ WE ARE ALL BORN SUPERSTARS ♪
♪ SHE ROLLED MY HAIR AND PUT
MY LIPSTICK ON IN THE GLASS ♪
♪ OF HER BOUDOIR "THERE'S
NOTHIN WRONG WITH LOVIN
WHO YOU ARE" ♪
♪ SHE SAID, "'CAUSE HE
MADE YOU PERFECT, BABE" ♪
♪ "SO HOLD YOUR HEAD UP
GIRL AND YOU'LL GO FAR, ♪
♪ LISTEN TO ME WHEN I
SAY" I'M BEAUTIFUL IN ♪
♪ MY WAY 'CAUSE GOD MAKES
NO MISTAKES I'M ON THE ♪
♪ RIGHT TRACK BABY I
WAS BORN THIS WAY DON'T ♪
♪ HIDE YOURSELF IN REGRET
JUST LOVE YOURSELF AND ♪
♪ YOU'RE SET I'M ON THE
RIGHT TRACK BABY I WAS ♪
♪ BORN THIS WAY OOO THERE
AIN'T NO OTHER WAY BABY ♪
♪ I WAS BORN THIS WAY
BABY I WAS BORN THIS ♪
♪ WAY OOO THERE AIN'T NO
OTHER WAY BABY I WAS ♪
♪ BORN- I'M ON THE RIGHT
TRACK BABY I WAS BORN ♪
♪ THIS WAY DON'T BE A
DRAG -JUST BE A QUEEN ♪
♪ DON'T BE A DRAG -JUST
BE A QUEEN DON'T BE A ♪
♪ DRAG -JUST BE A QUEEN
DON'T BE! GIVE YOURSELF ♪
♪ PRUDENCE AND LOVE YOUR
FRIENDS SUBWAY KID, ♪
♪ REJOICE YOUR TRUTH IN
THE RELIGION OF THE ♪
♪ INSECURE I MUST BE
MYSELF, RESPECT MY ♪
♪ YOUTH A DIFFERENT LOVER
IS NOT A SIN BELIEVE ♪
♪ CAPITAL H-I-M (HEY HEY
HEY) I LOVE MY LIFE I ♪
♪ LOVE THIS RECORD AND
MI AMORE VOLE FE YAH
(LOVE NEEDS FAITH) ♪
♪ I'M BEAUTIFUL IN MY WAY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE GOD MAKES NO MISTAKES ♪
♪ I'M ON THE RIGHT TRACK BABY ♪
♪ I WAS BORN THIS WAY ♪
♪ DON'T HIDE YOURSELF
IN REGRET ♪
♪ JUST LOVE YOURSELF
AND YOU'RE SET ♪
♪ I'M ON THE
RIGHT TRACK BABY ♪
♪ I WAS BORN THIS WAY ♪
♪ OOO THERE AIN'T
NO OTHER WAY ♪
♪ BABY I WAS BORN THIS WAY ♪
♪ OOO THERE AIN'T
NO OTHER WAY ♪
♪ BABY I WAS BORN THIS WAY ♪
♪ I'M ON THE RIGHT TRACK BABY ♪
♪ I WAS BORN THIS WAY ♪
♪♪♪
♪ DON'T BE A DRAG,
JUST BE A QUEEN ♪
♪ WHETHER YOU'RE BROKE OR
EVERGREEN ♪
♪ YOU'RE BLACK, WHITE, BEIGE,
CHOLA DESCENT ♪
♪ YOU'RE LEBANESE,
YOU'RE ORIENT ♪
♪ WHETHER LIFE'S DISABILITIES ♪
♪ LEFT YOU OUTCAST, BULLIED,
OR TEASED ♪
♪ REJOICE AND LOVE
YOURSELF TODAY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE BABY YOU WERE
BORN THIS WAY ♪
♪ NO MATTER GAY,
STRAIGHT, OR BI, ♪
♪ LESBIAN, TRANSGENDERED LIFE ♪
♪ I'M ON THE RIGHT TRACK BABY ♪
♪ I WAS BORN TO SURVIVE ♪
♪ NO MATTER BLACK,
WHITE OR BEIGE ♪
♪ CHOLA OR ORIENT MADE ♪
♪ I'M ON THE RIGHT TRACK BABY ♪
♪ I WAS BORN TO BE BRAVE ♪
♪ I'M BEAUTIFUL IN MY WAY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE GOD MAKES
NO MISTAKES ♪
♪ I'M ON THE RIGHT
TRACK BABY ♪
♪ I WAS BORN THIS WAY ♪
♪ DON'T HIDE YOURSELF
IN REGRET ♪
♪ JUST LOVE YOURSELF AND
YOU'RE SET ♪
♪ I'M ON THE RIGHT
TRACK BABY ♪
♪ I WAS BORN THIS WAY ♪
♪ OOO THERE AIN'T
NO OTHER WAY ♪
♪ BABY I WAS BORN THIS WAY ♪
♪ OOO THERE AIN'T
NO OTHER WAY ♪
♪ BABY I WAS BORN THIS WAY ♪
♪ I'M ON THE RIGHT
TRACK BABY ♪
♪ I WAS BORN THIS WAY ♪
♪ I WAS BORN THIS WAY HEY! ♪
♪ I'M ON THE RIGHT TRACK BABY ♪
♪ MUSIC FADES OUT.... ♪